Guide to the Yale University Building Project Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Project management records, circa 2004-2005; Accession 2006-A-095; 24.25; (29 boxes)
  - Central/Science WHIT 175 Office Rehab. Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 030114-02 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Central/Science WALL 53 Auditorium Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 020702-01 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Central/Science WHIT 55 5th Floor Invest. Fit-out Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 011116-01 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Central/Science WNSL High Bay Renovation Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 020925-01 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Central/Science WOOD Accessibilty Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 980223-10 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Central/Science WOOD Roof Replacement Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 001115-03 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Central/Science Yale field Roof Replacement Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 010712-01 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Central/Science York 200 Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 980223-12 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Central/Science Yale University Art Gallery Moving Operations Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 020228-01 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Central/Science Yale University Art Gallery/St Comprehensive Renovation Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 980223-31 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Central/Science Yale University Art Gallery temporary Woodshop Fit-out Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 030826-01 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Central/Science Physical Plant Relocation Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 010222-02 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Central/Science SPP Capacity Increase 2002 Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 990709-02 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Central/Science SPP Chilled Water Upgrade Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 030826-02 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Central/Science SPP Environmental Mod. Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 021209-01 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Central/Science SPP Fire Pump Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 030617-01 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Central/Science SPP Steam System Upgrade Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 030826-03 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Central/Science CRAF Non-Capital Projects Purchase Order Agreements F/Y 2003-2004 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Central/Science FRR7 Non-Capital Projects Purchase Order Agreements F/Y 2003-2004 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Central/Science FAC. Proj. MGMT. Non Capital Projects Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Central/Science OML 3rd and 4th floor Renovation Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 031113-01 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Central/Science OML Aquatic Modular Building Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 040517-02 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Central/Science OML Brownstone Restoration Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 030825-03 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Central/Science OML Leaded Glass Restoration Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 031024-01 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Central/Science Park 211 Interior Renovation Phase 1 Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 031001-01 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Central/Science Park 215 Electrical Upgrade Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 030825-02 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Central/Science Park 215 Renovation Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 020913-02 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Central/Science PC Renovation Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 980223-75 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Central/Science PM Exterior Tower Restoration Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 010727-01 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Central/Science PM/ESC Fuel Cell Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 021115-01 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Central/Science PROS 77 Trum 89-87 Renovation Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 020529-01 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Central/Science Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 030715-03 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Central/Science Pros 285 Relocation Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 011129-02 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Central/Science Pros 355 Rooms 109 and 110 Renovation Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 031205-03 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Central/Science PSPP Repl SCL Condensate Pipe Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 031121-01 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Central/Science PSPS Rehabilitation Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 980223-03 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Central/Science Tunnel Beams PSPP Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 031219-01 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Central/Science SCR Replacement Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 030724-01 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Central/Science New Chiller and Cooling Tower Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 980223-68 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Central/Science Metering System Upgrade Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 030813-01 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Central/ScienceChiller Plant Optimization Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 040513-01 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Central/Science Tunnel Beams PSPP Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 031219-01 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Central/Science Tunnel Wall PSSP to SCL Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 040109-01 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Central/Science Gas Meter Purchase Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 040521-01 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Central/Science FES Building Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 000127-03 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Central/Science GIBBS CW Piping Replace Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 040213-01 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Central/Science Grounds Maintenance Facility Improv Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 020614-02 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Central/Science HGS Basement Re-Trapping CRAF 04 Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 030919-01 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Central/Science HGS Bathroom Renovations Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 030522-03 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Central/Science HH Install Fire Alarm Systems Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 031103-01 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Central/Science HLH1 Renovation Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 980223-33 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Central/Science HLH 37 Renovation and Addition Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 020719-01 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Central/Science HLH 43 Accessibility Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 020514-01 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Central/Science HLH 52 Basement Renovation Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 031027-01 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Central/Science HLH 55 Basement Renovation Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 020412-01 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Central/Science HLH 56 Exterior Renovation Purchase Orders F/Y 2003-2004; 990209-01 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Science Hill Parking Garage - Proposal - Turner Construction 7/23/03; 020321-01 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Science Hill Parking Garage - Change Auth. - Haley and Aldrich; 020321-01 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Silliman College - Proposal for woodcarver (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Silliman College - Invoices - Herbert Newman and Partners; 980223-43 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - SML Phase 2 - Contract - SBRA 4/9/03 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - SML and CCL Phase 2 - Contract and Proposals - Shepley Bulfinch Richardson and Abbott; 020213-04 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - SOM - Drawing Review - 8/20/96 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - SOM Strageic Planing - Contracr and Invoices - Robert A.M. Stern; 030404-02 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - SPL - Elevator Bids and Project Requests; 010606-01 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Sprague Memorial Hall Renovation - Change Auth. and Contracts - Durell Builders; 980224-22 (Box 8, Folder 10-11)
  - Sprague Memorial Hall Renovation - Change Auth. and Contracts - Spiegal Zamecnik and Shah; 980224-22 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Sprague Memorial Hall Renovation - Contract change Orders - Turner Construction; 980224-22 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Sprague Memorial Hall Renovation - Change Auth. and Transmittal - Kuwabara Payne Mckenna; 980224-22 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Sprague Memorial Hall Renovation - Contract and Invoices - Turner Construction; 980224-22 (Box 8, Folder 15-17)
  - Sprague Memorial Hall Renovation - Contract and Invoices - KPMB; 980224-22 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Sprague Memorial Hall Renovation - Contract Order - Turner Construction; 980224-22 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Sprague Memorial Hall Renovation - Contracts - Turner Construction; 980224-22 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - SSS Roof and Masonry Repairs - contract and change authorizations - Superstructure Engineers, Architects; 980224-23 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - SSS Fire Protection - Contract and Change Auth. - S/L/A/M Collaborative; 980223-41 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - SSS 3rd floor - Change Order - S Monaco Painting and Building; 030603-01 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - SSS - Service Request - Fortin Electric; 030603-01 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Temple St. 370 - Change Auth. - Allanbrook Benic Czajka; 980223-44 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Temple St. 370 - Change Orders - Joseph Kelly; 980223-44 (Box 8, Folder 26-27)
  - Arts Area Planning Study - Project Request and Invoices - Polshek and Partners; 941018-01 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - BAC Inergen System - Contract and Invoices - Turner Construction; 040406-01 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Becton Engineering Infras. Improv. - Contract - R.M. Kliment Halsband Architects; 010730-01 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Becton 212 and 217 - Vontract and Invoice - Petra Corp.; 020802-01 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Becton Labs 322 and 420 Renovation - Invoices - Jade Construction; 010601-01 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Becton 611B Renovation - Contracts and Invoices - Petra Construction; 030626-01 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Becton Elevator Renovation - Invoices - Thyssen Elevator; 970922-05 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Becton 322 and 420 Renovation - Bid Information; 010601-01 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Beinecke Landscape Improvement - Contract - Charney Arch.; 010215-01 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - BRBL/SML - Contract - Gregg Wies Arch.; 021206-01 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - BRBL/SML - Contract - Pike Company; 021206-01 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Beinecke Rare Book Library - Transmittal letter - Charney Arch.; 031002-08 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Saybrook Post Renovation - Contract - Fusco Corp.; 011218-01 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Building Permit Issues - CT Building Code (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Campus Sidewalk landscape Main. - Contract - Joseph Kelly; 020531-01 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Campus Sidewalk landscape Main. - Contract - Elmer Laydon Construction; 020531-01 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Campus Sign System - Change Auth. - Rieneck and Rieneck; 991210-02 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Campus Sign System - Change Auth. - Strong Cohen; 991210-02
  - Canal/Lock Area Planning - Purchase Order - Cooper, Roberston and Partners; 001130-01
  - Canal/Lock Area Planning - Planning study - Dimeo Construction Co.; 001130-01
  - Central/Science Tunnel Asbestos - Contract - Petco Insulation Co.; 020501-02 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Central/Science Tunnel Asbestos Phase 4 - Contract - Petco Insulation Co.; 020501-02 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Chemistry Research Bldg. - Contract and Invoices - Cannon Design; 000121-02 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Chemistry Research Bldg. - Contract and Invoices - Sebesta Bloomberg and Assoc.; 000121-02 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - College St. Retainer Classic Cut stone (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Crown st. 341 Renovation - Contract - Giordano Construction; 020913-01 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Crown st. 341 Renovation - Transmittal - Charles Swanson; 020913-01
  - Davenport College - Contract - Sebesta Blomberg and Assoc.; 980223-77 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Davenport College - Project Management - Diversified Project Mang.; 980223-77 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Davenport / Pierson College - Contract - Genovese and Massaro; 980223-77 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Proffesional Construction Services - Lewis Finkel (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - TD College Renovation, Fusco Corporation- Contracts (Folder 1); 980223-56 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - TD College Renovation, Fusco Corporation- Contracts (Folder 2); 980223-56 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - TD Renovation, Elite Property Services, Inc- Contract Request; 980223-56 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - TD Renovation, Curtain Walls + Windows, Inc.- Service Request; 980223-56 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Undergraduate Astronomy Observatory, David Thompson Architects- Trans Letter; 030515-01 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Undergraduate Astronomy Observatory, Paragon Construction Company; 030515-01 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Yale Police Station, Cooper, Robertson and Partners (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - University Police Station, FFandE: Kaestle Boos; 980223-07 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - P.O.# P04793PCS- University Police Facility, Diggs Construction; 980223-07 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - P.O.# P03707PCS- V Renovation, Integrated Security Systems; 980223-71 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - P.O.# P01963PCS- Vanderbilt Hall Renovation, Whiting Turner Contracting Company; 980223-71 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Whitney, 221, HVAC Improvements, Giordano Construction Corporation; 000802-01 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - P.O.# P02804PCS-Whitney 55, 5th Floor. Investments Fit-Out, Centerbrook Architects; 011116-01 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - P.O.# P03711PCS- Whitney 55, 5th Floor. Investments, Linbeck Construction Corporation; 011116-01 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - P.O.# P02074PCS- Whitney 155/221 Alternate Service, JFK Company, Inc.; 000505-01 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Whitney 155/221 Alternative Service, Vanhelm Haywood and Shadford; 000505-01 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Yale University Art Gallery Renovation, Kahn Building Revised GMP (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - P.O.# P02185PCS- Yale University Art Gallery/ST Comprehensive Renovation, Turner Construction Company; 980223-31 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Yale University Art Gallery Renovation Enabling Project, Barr and Barr, Inc.; 980223-31 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - P.O.# P03842PCS- Yale University Art Gallery Moving Operations, Barr and Barr Inc.; 020228-01 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Yale University Art Gallery- Exhibition Design (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - P.O.# P03301PCS- Yale Corinthian Yacht Club Renovation, F.J. Dahill Co., Inc.; 980706-01 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Yale Corinthian Yacht Club, Noyes Vogt Architects; 980706-01 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Yale Field Re-roofing, F.J. Dahill Co., Inc.; 010712-01 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Yale Field Grandstand Roof Repl., Gregg and Wies Architects, Trans Letter; 010712-01 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Yale Meyers Forest Camp, Kenneth Boroson Architects, Trans Letter; 030403-02 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Yale Meyers Forest Camp, Rundale Construction Company; 030403-02 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - 200 York, RM and P- Contract Negotiation; 980223-12 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Engineering Research Building, Cesar Pelli and Associated Architects; 000120-01 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - P.O.# P03508PCS- Engineering Research Building, Whiting Turner Contracting Company; 000120-01 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - York 149, Freight Elevator Renovation, #010606-02 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Yale University Art Gallery Agreement, Staples and Charles Ltd. (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Park 211 Interior Renovation - Contract - Zampa Construction; 031001-10 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Park 211 Interior Renovation - Contract - Bridgeport Restoration; 031001-10 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Park 215 Renovation - Contract - Charney Arch; 020913-02 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Park 215 Renovation - Contract and Invoice - Joseph F Kelly; 020913-02 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - PWG CMRFQ lists / Subcontracts list (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - PWG Locker Rooms (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - PWG Locker Rooms Renovation - Performance and Payment Bond (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - PWG Natorium Feasibility study - Contract and Invoice - Ellerbe Becket; 020212-02 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Physical Plant Building - Invoices; 010222-02 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Physical Plant Relocation - Invoices - GSI Arch; 010222-02 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Physical Plant Relocation -Contract and Invoices - Fusco Corp; 010222-02 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Pierson College Renovation - CM Selection; 980223-75 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Pierson College Renovation - Contract and Invoice - Sebesta Blomberg; 980223-75 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Pierson College Renovation - Contract and Invoice - Integrated Security Systems; 980223-75 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Pierson College Renovation - Contract and Invoice - Kullman Industries; 980223-75 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Pierson College Renovation - Contract and Change Orders - Linbeck Construction Corp; 980223-75 (Box 11, Folder 16-17)
  - Pierson College Renovation - Contract and Invoices - Spiegel Zamecnik and Shah Inc.; 980223-75 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Pierson Sage Parking Renovation - Contracts and invoices - Walker Parking Consul.; 010402-02 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - SPP Capacity Increase - Contracts and Invoices - Herbert Newman and Partners; 990709-02 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - SPP - Transmittal Letter - WM Group Engineers; 970530-04 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - SPP Capacity Increase - Contracts and Invoices - WM Group Engineers; 990709-02 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - SPP Capacity Increase - Contracts and Invoices -O and G Industries; 990709-02 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - SPP Capacity Increase - Change Orders # 1- 7 -O and G Industries; 990709-02 (Box 11, Folder 24-25)
  - SPP Capacity Increase - Contracts and Invoices -O and G Industries; 990709-02 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Prospect Modular Building - Change Auth. - Bismark Construction; 010510-02 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Prospect 77 - Transmittal - Taylor Burns; 020529-01 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Prospect 77 - Contract and Invoices - Pike Company; 020529-01 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Prospect 285 Relocation - Contract and Invoices - Paragon Construction; 011129-02 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Prospect 285 Relocation - Contract and Invoices - Christopher Williams Arch.; 011129-02 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Prospect 355 Relocation - Contract and Invoices - Giordano Co.; 030721-01 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Branford and Saybrook College - Change Order - Fusco Corp.; 000407-02 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Sterling Hall of Medicine I Wing E Level - Change Order - CDS LLC; 000614-01 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Engineering Research - Change Auth. - Cesar Pelli and Assoc.; 000102-01 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Rudolph Building Renovation - Contract - Skidmore Owings and Merrill\; 001215-01 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Woodbridge Hall - Change Auth. and Contract - Charney Arch.; 010215-01 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Congress Ave. Bulding 300 Cedar - Change Orders - Whiting - Turner; 980518-01 (Box 12, Folder 6-7)
  - Congress Ave. Building 300 Cedar - Contract - HB Communications; 980518-01 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Congress Ave. Building 300 Cedar - Change Auth. - Terra Vac Corp.; 980518-01 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Congress Ave. Building 300 Cedar - Change Auth. - Payette; 980518-01 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Congress Ave. Building 300 Cedar - Change Orders - Whiting Turner; 980518-01 (Box 12, Folder 11-13)
  - Engineering Research Building, Curtain Wall, Cesar Pelli and Associates (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Environmental Science Facility, Visual Graphic Systems Inc., Contract Request; 931115-10 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - PM/ESC Fuel Cell, VIBRA CONN Inc; 021115-01 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Fuel Cell @ ESC; 021115-01 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - P.O.# P03874PCS- Hillhouse 52 Exterior Rehabilitiation, Giordano Construction; 011221-01 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Hillhouse 52, Basement Renovation, Giordano Construction Company, Inc.; 031027-01 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - P.O.# P04395PCS- Hillhouse 52, Basement Renovation, Helpern Architects; 031027-01 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - P.O.# P03247PCS- Hillhouse 55, Basement Renovation, Charney Architects; 020412-01 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Hillhouse 55, Basement Renovation; 020412-01 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - P.O.# P03873PCS- Hillhouse 55 Basement Renovation, Paragon Construction; 020412-01 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - P.O.# P01074PCS- KBR Infrastructure Improvement Plan, Hillier/ Vanderweil; 990430-01 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Kline Biology Tower Concourse Facility, Gregg and Weis Architects; 020131-01 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Kline Biology Tower Facility, Sordoni Skanska Construction Company; 020131-01 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Kline Biology Tower 442 and 5TH Floor, Gregg and Wies Architects; 020207-01 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - P.O.# P03239PCS- Kline Biology Tower 442 and 5TH Floor Renovation, Sordani Skanska Construction Company; 020207-01 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - P.O.# P03476PCS- Kline Biology Tower Exterior Renovation, Sordoni Skanska Consturciton Company; 020501-03 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Kline Biology Tower 2nd Floor Laboratory/ Office Renovation, Gregg and Wies; 020920-01 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - P.O.# P03679PCS- Kline Biology Tower 7 and 8 Floors Lab Renovations, Business Invirons; 020919-01 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Kline Biology Tower 2ND Floor, OML 1st Floor Renovation, Gregg and Wies Architects; 020920-01 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Kline Biology Tower 2ND Floor, OML 1st Floor Renovation, Sordoni Skanska Construction Company; 020920-01 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - P.O.# P04149PCS- Kline Biology Tower 2ND, OML 1st Floor Renovations; 020920-01 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Dave Gordon"s Copy of Proposal # 1478, Renovate Labs KGL (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - P.O.# P04182PCS- KGL Room 321 A-C Lab Renovation, Business Invirons; 030108-01 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - P.O.# P04283PCS- KGL Machine Shop Relocation, K Zampa Construction, LLC; 030715-05 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - P.O.# P04665PCS- LWR Interior Rehabilitation, Herbert S. Newman and Partners P.C.; 021119-01 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - P.O.# P04063PCS- Lapham Field House Boiler Replacement, Buckingham Routh Co.; 021217-03 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - ML Elevator Renovation Bids/ Info; 980224-34 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - P.O.# P03555PCS- OML Roof Replacement, Giordano Construction; 020214-01 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - OML 1st Fl Renovation, Gregg and Wies Architects; 030527-02 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Osborn Memorial Lab-3rd and 4th Fl- Skanska USA Building Inc.; 031113-01 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Hall of Graduate Studies Electrical Upgrade, Genovese and Massaro, Inc.; 001201-03 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Engineering Research Building, Curtain Wall, Cesar Pelli and Associates (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Branford College Renovation- Durell Builders; 960710-02 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Branford/Saybrook Comprehensive Renovation- Perry Dean Rogers and Partners; 960710-02 (Box 14, Folder 2-3)
  - Branford and Saybrook Colleges Move Coordination- The S/L/A/M Collaborative; 960710-02 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Branford and Saybrook Renovation- Spiegel Zamecnik and Shah Inc.; 960710-07 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - BR (Branford and Saybrook) Renovation- Walgreen. The Care of Trees, Inc.; 960710-02 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - ESH Dorm and Apt Renovations- Baddidge Facilities Construction Company, Inc.; 980515-03 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - ES Harkness Dormitory and Apartments- Building Renovation and Sys Upgrade- Svigals and Ass.; 9809515-03 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - ESH Dorm and Apt Renovations- R.G. Vanderweil Engineers; 980515-03 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Kline Biology Tower Infrastructure- Improvement Plan, Priority 2- Sordoni Skanska Inc.; 010109-02 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Saybrook College Phase II- Perry Dean Rogers and Partners Architects; 000407-02 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Saybrook College Renovation, The S/L/A/M Collaborative; 000407-02 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Saybrook College Renovation, Spiegel Zamecnik and Shah, Inc; 000407-02 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Saybrook College Renovation, Barclay White-Construction; 000407-02 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Saybrook College Renovation- CM Fusco (Construction); 000407-02 (Box 14, Folder 15-18)
  - Saybrook College Renovation, Fusco Corporation; 000407-02 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - SY Post Renovation- Fusco Corporation; 011218-01 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Sterling Hall of Medicine C2 Lab Renovation- The Whiting-Turner Company; 010307-01 (Box 14, Folder 21-22)
  - Branford and Saybrook Renovation- Barclay White Incorporated; 960710-02 (Box 14, Folder 23-25)
  - Branford and Saybrook Renovation- Barclay White Incorporated; 960710-02 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Branford and Saybrook Colleges Compehesive Renovation- Barclay White Incorporated; 960710-02 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Timothy Dwight College Renovation- Peter Gisolfi Associates; 980223-56 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Timothy Dwight College Renovation- Integrated Security Systems; 980223-56 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Timothy Dwight College Renovation- Turner Construction Company; 980223-56 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - TD College Comprehensive Renovation- Peter Gisolfi Architects; 980223-56 (Box 15, Folder 6-7)
  - OML Prospect Wing, Sordoni Skanska; 970603-01 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - OML Prospect St. Wing- Hillier International, Inc.; 970603-01 (Box 15, Folder 9)